<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hospital</string>
    <string name="gender_prompt">Select Gender</string>
    <string name="medical_condition_prompt">Select Medical Condition</string>
    <string name="Male_reproductive_system" >
        <h1>Male Anatomy Explained\n</h1>
    <p>It’s a common myth that men think about sex every seven seconds.
        However, a study conducted at Ohio State University suggests the real number is likely closer to 19 times a day.
        Regardless of the figure, you can guarantee most of those thoughts concern getting busy between the sheets, and not what happens in the body.
        A lot of men have no idea how wonderfully complex their anatomy actually is, but I’m here to offer some insights.\n
    </p><br/>
        <h2>PENIS: MAN’S BEST FRIEND\n</h2><br/>
    <p>The penis is the part of the reproductive system men are most familiar with because it’s the organ used in sexual intercourse and masturbation.
        It actually has three parts: the root, the body, and the glans penis or head.
        The root attaches to the abdominal wall.
        The body’s three chambers fill with blood to cause an erection.
        If blood flow is compromised, erectile dysfunction occurs.
        The glans penis has a high concentration of nerve endings which makes sex pleasurable.\n</p><br/>
        <h2>SCROTUM: HOLDS TESTES AND REGULATES TEMPERATURE\n</h2><br/>
    <p>The scrotum is a sack of skin and muscles that houses the testes.
        The scrotum helps keep the testes away from the body, so they’re cool for optimal sperm development\n.</p><br/>
        <h2>TESTES: SPERM AND TESTOSTERONE PRODUCERS\n</h2><br/>
        <p>The testes are two glands which produce sperm and testosterone.
        If the testes don’t work effectively, you may have a low sperm count and low testosterone levels.
            While the terms testicles and testes are often used interchangeably, the testicles are actually the testes and their surrounding structures.\n</p><br/>
    <p>After the testes make sperm, the sperm travels to the epididymis to grow.
        During sexual arousal, contractions send the mature sperm on their way.
        An epididymal obstruction can sometimes form, causing infertility, but this can be diagnosed and effectively treated.\n</p><br/>
        <h2>VAS DEFERENS AND SEMINAL VESICLES: AID EJACULATION\n</h2><br/>
    <p>Together the vas deferens and seminal vesicles form the ejaculatory duct.
        Sperm from the epididymis reaches the vas deferens, then travels to the seminal vesicles where it joins with fluids to become semen.
        During ejaculation, muscles surrounding the seminal vesicles expel the semen.
        Up to 30% of men can experience premature ejaculation, while many men, particularly as they age, may experience delayed ejaculation.\n</p><br/>
        <h2>PROSTATE GLAND: MAKES PROSTATIC FLUID\n</h2><br/>
    <p>The prostate produces prostatic fluid. This white fluid nourishes, protects, and supports sperm, and is the major component in semen.\n</p><br/>
    <h2>URETHRA: EMPTIES BODILY FLUID\n</h2><br/>
    <p>The urethra is the final stop before sperm leaves the body during an orgasm.
        This tube works double-duty, also carrying urine from the bladder.
        During an erection, urine flow is blocked to ensure only semen leaves the body during an orgasm.\n</p><br/>
    <p><i>The next time you think about sex, remember all the complex parts of your body that are involved in the process.
    Such an amazing system should never be taken for granted.\n</i></p><br/></string>

    <string-array name="gender_array">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="medical_condition_array">
        <item>HIV</item>
        <item>Diabetes</item>
        <item>Hypertension</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>